{
    "subject": "resource/Verran_Sparebank",
    "predicate": "property/location",
    "object": "resource/Norway",
    "human_readable": "Verran Sparebank is located in Norway.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8959202766418457,
            "question": "Where is Verran Sparebank located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8863635659217834,
            "question": "In which country is Verran Sparebank situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6898308396339417,
            "question": "What is the climate like in the region where Verran Sparebank is located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6796695590019226,
            "question": "Is Verran Sparebank located in Europe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6426815986633301,
            "question": "Can you name other banks located in Norway?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5435919761657715,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks near Verran Sparebank?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46854791045188904,
            "question": "What type of institution is Verran Sparebank?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36521998047828674,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges facing banks in Norway?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29337024688720703,
            "question": "What services does Verran Sparebank likely provide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29182642698287964,
            "question": "Does Verran Sparebank have a website?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Verran Sparebank is located in Norway.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6489_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What services does Verran Sparebank likely provide?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6489_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the challenges facing banks in Norway?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6489_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of institution is Verran Sparebank?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6489_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6489_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6489_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6489_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6489_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6489_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6489_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6489_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6489_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6489_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6489_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6489/re-ranker-msmarco/4.txt mentions that Verran Sparebank was a Norwegian savings bank, located at Venneshamn in Mosvik municipality from 1907 to 2006."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Verran Sparebank's location and its association with Norway, confirming that it was indeed located in Norway. Specifically, the document states \"Verran Sparebank was a Norwegian savings bank\" and provides details on its location within Mosvik municipality in Norway."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}